{
    "id": "33f7c3a387b6488bad508b21cf1d9e80",
    "title": "Linking Words Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": ".....................… I fired at the lion, he shook my arm.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "Since",
                "Because",
                "While"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "31e11a3e90f44dc2a671e4058a79f002"
        },
        {
            "question": "Arranged marriages are quite unusual in the West. In Asia, ..................... ., they are very common.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in spite of this",
                "similarly",
                "on the other hand",
                "In addition"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "159c5f9d032d489bb7fbfe0ce26fed17"
        },
        {
            "question": "The job was not quite exciting. ......................., the money was OK",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Due to this",
                "Mind you",
                "While",
                "In addition"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c5e388d52abe4a789633a8b5efd464e4"
        },
        {
            "question": "The train was late. .....................… I reached in time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "In spite this",
                "Despite this",
                "Due to this",
                "Owing to this"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "606368d34d0c4231b069ccc04c0f491b"
        },
        {
            "question": "The British rule may have benefited India in some ways. ..................... colonialism is basically bad.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Even as",
                "Even so",
                "In the same way",
                "Similarly"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4b63d43b31474db7921975cb00c321ed"
        },
        {
            "question": "Life has ....................... been good to me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as for",
                "as far as",
                "apart from",
                "generally"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "9b956c2eb1db417688ab70e48e27dd5e"
        },
        {
            "question": "The flood victims are short of food. ...................... they urgently need medical assistance.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "In addition",
                "Similarly",
                "For instance",
                "Any how"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d23c25907244437b82efa80511b37f5b"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………….. John, everyone enjoyed the party.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "In addition to",
                "Except for",
                "In particular"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6bb3c9077d974eebb95e627349529493"
        },
        {
            "question": "...................... people will be nice to you if you are nice to them.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Apart from",
                "In most cases",
                "In the same way",
                "For instance"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e656b303ff144a0aab94db1e2f7baacb"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………….. a child’s character is shaped by the circumstances at home.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Similarly",
                "For one thing",
                "To a great extent",
                "Consequently"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b1a9016d0c4e43e680c522f3126cfd4b"
        }
    ]
}